JUAN C. BARRIOS S.

FRONT END DEVELOPER

SKILLS PROFESSIONALS

JavaScript
TypeScript
React
Next
Node with Express
Flutter
React Native

SKILLS PERSONALS

Creative
Trustworthy and professional
Organized
Time management
Teamwork
Fast learner
Motivated
Funny

CONTACT

+58 4121556808 juanbarrios045@gmail.com https://juanbs.com/

REFERENCES

JUNIOR SÁNCHEZ

Developer FullStack jysa65.dev@gmail.com

LENNON PEREZ

Front End Developer lenonart14@gmail.com

PROFILE

My name is Juan, I'm 22 years old and I'm from Venezuela. I am a big fan of web development and technology. I am completely passionate about everything I do so that it is the best of the best, I am creative, fun and I assure you that I will make you smile if you meet me.

I'm a Front End Developer with more than four year of work experience.



EXPERIENCE

TAUROS

Nov 2019 - Feb 2023

Bring the design to the web using React.js, adapting it to various devices and browsers, using the help of APIs to connect the web with various services or systems.

FREELANCER

Sep 2019 - Present

Offer my services to companies or people who need a solution to their problems through web or mobile development.

ACADEMIC COACH

Jun 2018 - Jun 2020

Teach through extra classes and workshops to help students perform better.

EDUCATION

SYSTEMS ANALYST

Instituto Universitario de Tecnología para la informatica | 2017 - 2020